

MOUMINATOU BARRY

DESIGNER | DEVELOPER | EDUCATOR

PROFILE

I have 10 years as an Entrepreneur & self-taught full-stack Developer. My prowess in Designing & Engineering allows me to merge Business and Tech to leverage a product needs and then prove/design client solutions.

My abilities to think creatively and strategically, allows me to build trust, and communicate product enhancements, supportability plans, and profit.

CONTACT

MoeBarry13@gmail.com 347-501-6112 @Moe_Techtainment MoeTechtainment.com

Linkedin.com/SuccessfulEntreprenuer13/

EDUCATION

The Knowledge House 2016 | 2019- Computer Science, Product Dev, Hardware

Year Up NY '20 2016 - Digital Marketing

Hunter College 2015 - Computer Science

Democracy Prep Charter High School 2014 - Advance Regents Diploma

SKILLS

<A/B, Card Sort, User Testing />

Advocating
Advertising
AutoDesk Fusion 360

Affinity Diagramming /> Customer Service />

<HTML5 /> <CSS3 />

<Guerilla Marketing />

<ES8 />

<KPI />

<Monetization />

<Prototyping /> <SEM />

Adobe Creative Cloud • • • • • •

BACK-END • • • •

CONTENT CREATION

- - 00004

FRONT-END

MICROSOFT SUITES

TEACHING •••••

UX/UI ••••

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Oath Tumblr | 2018 - 2019

- Designed user-centered apps/websites, & advertised preferences in order to increase KPI's and Sales
- Led the merge between Engineering & Product Design to create more efficient/creative features
- Learned, Created & Taught team members components with REACT.js framework to optimize metrics

CREATIVE DIRECTOR

Mogul Media | 2018 - 2019

- Created Commercials, Electronic Press Kits, & Websites for Artist/Influencers like Cashflow Harlem, Cardi B, Fashion Nova while increasing presence & value
- Assisted & Managed teammates to push Artist/Influencers to gain at least 1,000 followers during promotions using SEO/SEM
- Professional development for underground Artist/Influencers by enhancing etiquette, pitches, and branding by 80%

TECH INSTRUCTOR

The Knowledge House | 2017 - 2019

- Developed Apps with (M)ongoDB (E)xpress (A)ngular (N)odeJs & Ionic Framework to create fast scalable servers
- Instructed 50+ Fordham University STEP students on the fundamentals of coding & entrepreneurship
- Managed & guided coworkers to ensure creative curriculums & timely service launches & to meet deadlines
- Taught 20+ Mohegan Prep Elementary scholars how to use Cognitive thinking within Robotics & Coding

HEAD COACH

Westside Hoops | 2014 - 2019

- Created 20 + graphic & digital designs for social media marketing
- Led practices & trips across NYC, while incorporating Moe Techtainment so athletes could see how Math & Science are relative to our everyday lives
- Recruited, Interviewed & Trained potential coaches on the fundamentals of basketball & how to communicate/work with children
- Taught & Learned with 100+ Pre K-6 graders across NYC about the fundamentals of basketball, good sportsmanship, strategizing & team work

OPERATIONS MANAGER

Democracy Prep HQ | 2014 - 2016

- Facilitated teams & contributed to decorating & organizing 20+ galas/street fairs
- Listened to 100+ consumer ideas & created creative, business, & tech solutions
- Processed 500+ Invoices & Receipts to ensure quality tax processes
- S.T.E.A.M advocate & mentor for all 7 site locations in NYC

INTRA/ENTREPRENUERSHIP

Microsoft BAM - Code Instructor, Mentor, Volunteer

United Nations - Influencer for the Sustainable Development Goals: Well Being & Education



Democracy Prep

Google Cloud FLOC

helps people understand the relationships between STE(A)M & Reality by using Cognitive and Experimental learning.

Pedagogy consists of Chess, Coding & Entreprenuership.

All-Star Code Harlem Business Alliance

Communitas America JPM Chase | Advancing Black Pathways

Community Events The Knowledge House

NFTE | GENTECH NYC STEM Kids Power of You Teens Silicon Harlem StartUp Bus Success Academy

Thurgood Marshall Academy